[{
    "questionNumber": 1,
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Bokbytaren",
    "correctAnswer": "Kobe Bryant",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },{
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Jetens yror",
    "correctAnswer": "Terry Jones",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },{
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Gudalik sork",
    "correctAnswer": "Kirk Douglas",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Olle lagman",
    "correctAnswer": "Ola Magnell",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },{
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Brough teflon",
    "correctAnswer": "Olof Thunberg",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Braka inomhus",
    "correctAnswer": "Hosni Mubarak",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Snowy vax mod",
    "correctAnswer": "Max von Sydow",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Ekorrens gny",
    "correctAnswer": "Kenny Rogers",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Sandig lama",
    "correctAnswer": "Adam Alsing",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Herr Dillcitat",
    "correctAnswer": "Little Richard",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Hornet ni knep",
    "correctAnswer": "Henrik Pont√©n",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Lo i hamn",
    "correctAnswer": "Ian Holm",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Oron i ceremonin ",
    "correctAnswer": "Ennio Morricone",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Nio halvvilda ideal",
    "correctAnswer": "Olivia de Havilland",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Combined hacksaw",
    "correctAnswer": "Chadwick Boseman",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "BRIS hungrar budget",
    "correctAnswer": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "De hade inavel",
    "correctAnswer": "Eddie Van Halen",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Annoy screen",
    "correctAnswer": "Sean Connery",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Vent or swell",
    "correctAnswer": "Sven Wollter",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Niagara doomed",
    "correctAnswer": "Diego Maradona",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "Jarl och nere",
    "correctAnswer": "John le Carre",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  }
]

